Guide to the Gay Alliance of the Genesee Valley records, 1970-2012.
Gay Alliance of the Genesee Valley records,
- Series III. Empty Closet
  - Alphabetical Subject Files 1971-1984 (First Donation)
    - G-L
      - Gays and money, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 61)
      - Gays and the Bible, 1977-1981 (Box 8, Folder 62)
      - Gays and the church, 1975-1977 (Box 8, Folder 63)
      - Gays and the law, 1972-1979 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - "Gays and the Law: A Guide for Laypeople" brochure, Undated (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - Gays and the military, 1975,1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - Gays on campus, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Gays on the Hill, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      - Gay teachers, 1981-1982 (Box 9, Folder 6)
      - Gay teachers, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 7)
      - Gay Teachers Association, 1977-1979 (Box 9, Folder 8)
      - Gay TV program articles, 1977,1980-1981 (Box 9, Folder 9)
      - Gay youth, Undated (Box 9, Folder 10)
      - Gay youth, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 11)
      - Genesee Mental Heatlh Center brochures, Undated (Box 9, Folder 12)
      - Genesee Valley Presbytery News, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 13)
      - "Got a Problem" brochure, Undated (Box 9, Folder 14)
      - Gov. Northrup, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 15)
      - "Growing Up Gay" pamphlet, Undated (Box 9, Folder 16)
      - GWARM Monitor, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 17)
      - HALO Grapevine, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 18)
      - "Has the FBI Been in Your Closet?" article, Undated (Box 9, Folder 19)
      - Hatch Act, Undated (Box 9, Folder 20)
      - Health, general, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 21)
      - Homophobia, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 22)
      - Homosexual Counseling Journal, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 23)
      - Human Rights Campaign Fund candidate questionnaire, Undated (Box 9, Folder 24)
      - Human rights- booklets, 1973-1974,1976 (Box 9, Folder 25)
      - Human rights, 1972-1974 (Box 9, Folder 26)
      - Immigration, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 27)
      - Immigration- petition, Undated (Box 9, Folder 28)
      - Information pamphlets- gay issues, 1975-1978 (Box 9, Folder 29)
      - Integrity brochures, Undated (Box 9, Folder 30)
      - Integrity international, 1976-1977 (Box 9, Folder 31)
      - International Gay News Agency press release, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 32)
      - It's Time (NGTF newsletter), 1976-1979 (Box 9, Folder 33)
      - IWY/IWD, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 34)
      - Jack Campbell, Undated (Box 9, Folder 35)
      - Jean-Paul Goude autobiography press release, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 36)
      - Kennedy, Senator Edward, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 37)
      - King, Billie Jean, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 38)
      - Koch- NYC Mayor, 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 39)
      - Lambda Legal Defense, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 40)
      - Lambda Legal Defense Fund awards dinner invitation, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 41)
      - Lavender Special newsletter, Ithaca, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 42)
      - Legal/political, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 43)
      - Lesbian mothers, Undated (Box 9, Folder 44)
      - Lesbian mothers, 1977-1981 (Box 9, Folder 45)
      - Lesbian mothers/custody, 1981? (Box 9, Folder 46)
      - "Let's All Be Gay at City Lights" flyer, Undated (Box 9, Folder 47)
      - Letters to the Editor- gay, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 48)
      - "List of Journals Indexed", Undated (Box 9, Folder 49)
      - Local media, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 50)
      - Local media, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 51)
      - Local media, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 52)
      - Local media, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 53)
      - Local media, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 54)
      - Local media, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 55)
      - Local media, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 56)
      - Local media, 1980? (Box 9, Folder 57)
    - M-S
      - Macaluso, Michael, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 58)
      - Magazine articles, 1972, 1977-1979 (Box 9, Folder 59)
      - Information on Making Love the movie, Undated (Box 9, Folder 60)
      - Maps, Undated (Box 9, Folder 61)
      - Maps of Rochester (bars & amp; baths), Undated (Box 9, Folder 62)
      - March on Pentagon, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 63)
      - March on Washington brochure, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 64)
      - Market Info- Business Week, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 65)
      - Matlovich, Leonard, 1975-1978 (Box 9, Folder 66)
      - Mattachine, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 67)
      - McDonald Amendment, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 68)
      - Media, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 69)
      - Media, 1981-1982 (Box 9, Folder 70)
      - Media, 1981-1983 (Box 9, Folder 71)
      - Media, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 72)
      - Media, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 73)
      - Media- CBS- "Gay Power, Gay Politics", 1980 (Box 9, Folder 74)
      - Media- Miscellaneous, 1981-1982 (Box 10, Folder 1)
      - Media- politics, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 2)
      - Media- religious, 1980-1981 (Box 10, Folder 3)
      - Metropolitan Community Church brochures, Undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
      - MCC Miscellaneous, 1976-1980 (Box 10, Folder 5)
      - MCC flyer, Undated (Box 10, Folder 6)
      - Milk, Harvey, 1977-1979 (Box 10, Folder 7)
      - Mike & amp; Paul, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 8)
      - Miscellaneous, 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      - Miscellaneous article copies, news clippings, 1979-1982 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      - Miscellaneous pamphlets, brochures, Undated (Box 10, Folder 11)
      - Miscellaneous Rochester materials, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 12)
      - Miscellaneous Syracuse brochures, 1982, 1985? (Box 10, Folder 13)
      - Moral Majority, 1980-1981 (Box 10, Folder 14)
      - Musical groups, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 15)
      - NAMBLA, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 16)
      - NAM: Working Papers on Socialism & amp; Feminism, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 17)
      - National Association of Gay & amp; Lesbian Democratic Clubs conference, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 18)
      - National Council of Churches, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 19)
      - National Democratic Party, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 20)
      - National Endowment of the Arts, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 21)
      - National Endowment for the Humanities, 1977-1978 (Box 10, Folder 22)
      - National Gay Archives brochure, Undated (Box 10, Folder 23)
      - News clippings, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 24)
      - News clippings (Box 10, Folder 25-28)
      - News clippings, 1980-1981 (Box 10, Folder 29)
      - News clippings, 1981-1982 (Box 10, Folder 30)
      - News clippings, 1970s (Box 10, Folder 31)
      - News reprints- National Gay Rights Bill/Rep. McDonald's anti-gay resolution, 1979? (Box 10, Folder 32)
      - The New World, 1982? (Box 10, Folder 33)
      - NGTF- "About Coming Out" pamphlet, Undated (Box 10, Folder 34)
      - NGTF civil rights support packet, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 35)
      - NGTF media brochures, Undated (Box 10, Folder 36)
      - NGTF- "20 Questions About Homosexuality", 1978? (Box 10, Folder 37)
      - NGTF Miscellaneous, 1977-1980 (Box 10, Folder 38)
      - NGTF Miscellaneous, 1974,1976-1978 (Box 10, Folder 39)
      - Noble, Elaine, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 40)
      - NOW, 1973-1974,1977-1980 (Box 10, Folder 41)
      - New York Civil Liberties Union mailing, Undated (Box 10, Folder 42)
      - NY legislative impact guide, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 43)
      - NYS Assembly summary of legislation on women's issues, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 44)
      - NYS Lesbian and Gay Political Alliance, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 45)
      - Oneonta Gayzette, 1975-1978 (Box 10, Folder 46)
      - Organizations, 1971-1973,1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 47)
      - OZ helpline, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 48)
      - The Pacific Center, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 49)
      - Patriot publication, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 50)
      - Planned Parenthood, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 51)
      - Planned Parenthood "Straight Talk" program packet, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 1)
      - Politics- candidates and statements, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 2)
      - Politics- Gay Political Caucus, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 3)
      - Postcards/notecards, Undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
      - Presbyterians for Lesbian and Gay Concerns, 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 5)
      - Prisoners, 1977-1980 (Box 11, Folder 6)
      - Prisoners- gay, Undated (Box 11, Folder 7)
      - Prostitution, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 8)
      - "Provincetown 1985" brochure, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 9)
      - "Questions About the Draft for Lesbians and Gays" proposed final text, Undated (Box 11, Folder 10)
      - Rainbow flyer, Undated (Box 11, Folder 11)
      - "Raising Free Children" article, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 12)
      - Rape Crisis Center, Undated (Box 11, Folder 13)
      - Rape Crisis Service, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 14)
      - Rape Crisis Services, Undated (Box 11, Folder 15)
      - Religious pamphlets, newsletter, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 16)
      - Religious periodicals, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 17)
      - Religious positions on homosexuality, 1969-1974 (Box 11, Folder 18)
      - Religious response to homosexuality, 1975-1980 (Box 11, Folder 19)
      - Religious statements on homosexuality, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 20)
      - Republican (headquarters), 1979 (Box 11, Folder 21)
      - Responses to APA decision, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 22)
      - Rites, Feb. 1986 (Box 11, Folder 23)
      - Rivendell Marketing Co. brochure, Undated (Box 11, Folder 24)
      - Rochester map, Undated (Box 11, Folder 25)
      - RWAVAW, 1977-1979 (Box 11, Folder 26)
      - Sappho (lesbian substance abuse rehab center) brochure, Undated (Box 11, Folder 27)
      - Seattle Gay Guide, 1983-1984 (Box 11, Folder 28)
      - Sex discrimination, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 29)
      - Sexuality- theories- publications, 1971, 1974-1979 (Box 11, Folder 30)
      - Siemens Corporation article reprints, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 31)
      - Signal (Gay Nurses Alliance publication), 1981 (Box 11, Folder 32)
      - Sign Language, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 33)
      - Sisterhood- and my Brothers short story by Rima Shore, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 34)
      - Consensual sodomy law, 1973-1975 (Box 11, Folder 35)
      - Sodomy law repeal information, 1976-1980 (Box 11, Folder 36)
      - Consensual sodomy ruling, Undated (Box 11, Folder 37)
      - Consensual sodomy laws, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 38)
      - "Statement to the Movement from Gay Revolutionaries in Yellow Springs, Ohio", Undated (Box 11, Folder 39)
      - Stonewall Report, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 40)
      - Struttin' Up 5th, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 41)
      - Student-oriented Program, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 42)
      - Syracuse, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 43)
      - Syracuse area publications, 1975-1977 (Box 11, Folder 44)
    - T-Z
      - Talisman publication, Hunter College, Winter, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 45)
      - Three Rivers Arts Festival, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 46)
      - Threshold, Undated (Box 11, Folder 47)
      - Tom Wilson, Undated (Box 11, Folder 48)
      - Transsexuals, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 49)
      - Transvestites, 1976-1979 (Box 11, Folder 50)
      - Trish Nugent- Foxglove Woman poster, Undated (Box 11, Folder 51)
      - University of Rochester Gay Academic Union "Word is Out" Flyer, Undated (Box 11, Folder 52)
      - US Civil Rights Commission, 1977,1981 (Box 11, Folder 53)
      - US government memos re: extortion, sex offenders, etc., 1974? (Box 11, Folder 54)
      - US Supreme Court, 1977-1979 (Box 11, Folder 55)
      - UUGC press release re: protest, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 56)
      - Violence, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 57)
      - Washington Report, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 58)
      - What Jesus Said About Homosexuality flyer, Undated (Box 11, Folder 59)
      - White, Dan- San Francisco, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 60)
      - "Who Represents You" flyer distributed by the Leauge of Women Voters/Rochester Metro area, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 61)
      - WIN: Workshop In Nonviolence, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 62)
      - Women- women's liberation, 1971, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 63)
      - Women and politics, 1974-1974, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 64)
      - Women in Sunlight, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 65)
      - Workshops on homosexuality, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 66)
      - Youth Advocacy project, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 67)
      - Youth liberation, Undated (Box 11, Folder 68)
      - Youth Services Guide of Monroe County, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 69)
      - Human rights, 1967? (Box 12, Folder 4)
      - Bumper stickers (March on Washington, Mains for Council), Mains for Council pin, Undated (Box 12, Folder 5)
      - Legal rulings, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 7)
      - News clippings, 1975-1977 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Alphabetical Subject Files 1975-2004 (Second Donation)
    - A-F
      - AAPHR (assoc. of physicians for human rights), 1993-1994 (Box 13, Folder 1)
      - AAPHR (assoc. of physicians for human rights), 1995-2001 (Box 13, Folder 2)
        Name of organization changed to Gay and Lesbian Medical Association
      - Catherine Abate, 1992, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 3)
      - Abdill and Ellis Killing, 1995-1996 (Box 13, Folder 4)
      - Abortion, 1989-1992, 2000-2002 (Box 13, Folder 5)
      - Academy Awards, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 6)
      - Roberta Achtenberg, 1993, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 7)
      - Action for a better Community, 2001-2002 (Box 13, Folder 8)
        Annual report
      - ACLU Gay Rights (1), 1990-1993, 1996-1997 (Box 13, Folder 9)
        Includes legal dockets.
      - ACLU Gay Rights (2), 1998-2001 (Box 13, Folder 10)
        Legal dockets, reports
      - Adoption, 1989-2003 (Box 13, Folder 11)
      - Advertising, c. 1988-1999 (Box 13, Folder 12)
      - Affirmation Methodists, 1987-1989 (Box 13, Folder 13)
      - Affirmation Mormons, Undated (Box 13, Folder 14)
      - African American Gays, 1987-2001 (Box 13, Folder 15)
        Photo (Undated)
      - Aging, 1992-1995 (Box 13, Folder 16)
        Conference programs
      - AIDS, 1987-1991, 1995, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 17)
      - AIDS Action Council, 1993-1997, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 18)
      - AIDS Action Front Center (ABC), c. 1994-1999 (Box 13, Folder 19)
        Includes annual report
      - AIDS Activism – Local including Act Up, c. 1988-1993, 1997, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 20)
      - AIDS Activism - National including Act Up, 1989-2001 (Box 13, Folder 21)
      - AIDS Alternative Therapies, 1996-1997 (Box 13, Folder 22)
      - AIDS and Anemia, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 23)
        Information packet
      - AIDS and Aspirin, 1994-1996 (Box 13, Folder 24)
      - AIDS and AZT, 1987-1989 (Box 13, Folder 25)
        Includes price survey
      - AIDS - Blood Supplies, 1987-1990, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 26)
      - AIDS and the Arts, 1988-1997 (Box 13, Folder 27)
      - AIDS and Blindness, c. 1995 (Box 13, Folder 28)
      - AIDS - Books and Literature, c. 1982-1989 (Box 13, Folder 29)
      - AIDS - Budget Allocations, Rochester, Monroe County, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 30)
        Monroe County Interdepartmental Correspondence
      - AIDS - Budget Allocations, New York State, 1988-1990, 1995, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 31)
      - AIDS - Budget Allocations, Federal, 1988-2001 (Box 13, Folder 32)
      - AIDS - Buffalo, c. 1988, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 33)
        Research paper.
      - AIDS and the Catholic Church, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 34)
      - AIDS and Chemical Dependency, 1988, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 35)
        Pamphlet
      - AIDS - Clinics, National, c. 1999 (Box 13, Folder 36)
        Pamphlet and survey.
      - AIDS - Colleges, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 37)
      - AIDS - CHN, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 38)
      - AIDS - Condoms, 1987-1988, 1995, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 39)
      - AIDS - Conferences, 1989-2000 (Box 13, Folder 40)
        Includes surveys and conference schedules
      - AIDS - Counseling, c. 1993, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 41)
      - AIDS and the Deaf, c. 1994 (Box 13, Folder 42)
      - AIDS - Dental Care, 1988-1993 (Box 13, Folder 43)
      - AIDS - Disclosure and Contact Tracing, 1987-1989 (Box 13, Folder 44)
        Senate bills and documents
      - AIDS - Discrimination, 1986-2001 (Box 13, Folder 45)
        NYS legislative assembly memorandum, emails
      - AIDS - Drug Research and Testing, 1997-2002 (Box 14, Folder 1)
        Includes drug information and ingredients
      - AIDS - Drug Therapy (1), 1987-1995 (Box 14, Folder 2)
        Includes drug information, patient tests, graphs, information packets, and essays
      - AIDS - Drug Therapy (2), 1995-1998 (Box 14, Folder 3)
      - AIDS - Drug Therapy (3), 1998-1999, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 4)
      - AIDS - Drug Therapy (4), 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 5)
        Includes pamphlets, fact sheets, press releases, media packets, letters, forms, and conference schedule
      - AIDS - Education (1), 1986-1995 (Box 14, Folder 6)
        Includes brochures, Letters to the House of Representatives, senate action documents, other articles, and media packet
      - AIDS - Education (2), 1995-2002 (Box 14, Folder 7)
        Includes media packets, viewers guide, brochures
      - AIDS - Drug Resistant Virus Strains, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 8)
      - AIDS - Local Education, 1988-1991, 1995-1997 (Box 14, Folder 9)
      - AIDS - Electricity (as "cure"), 1995-1996 (Box 14, Folder 10)
        Includes treatment and device information and diagram
      - AIDS - Employment, 1986-1988 (Box 14, Folder 11)
        Includes -proposed legislation draft
      - AIDS - Family, 1993-1995 (Box 14, Folder 12)
      - AIDS - Scott Evertz, c. 2001 (Box 14, Folder 13)
      - AIDS - Fundraisers, Local, 1987-2000 (Box 14, Folder 14)
      - AIDS - Fundraisers, National (1), 1988-1997 (Box 14, Folder 15)
        Includes National AIDS Advisory Board Members, OUTNY'94 issue, media packets
      - AIDS - Fundraisers, National (2), 1997-2001 (Box 14, Folder 16)
      - AIDS - Gay Men's Health Crisis (GMHC), 1988-1999 (Box 14, Folder 17)
      - AIDS and George W. Bush, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 18)
      - AIDS - Helms Amendment, 1987-1988 (Box 14, Folder 19)
        Includes Congressional Records
      - AIDS Healthcare Foundation (Policy Watch), 1997 (Box 14, Folder 20)
        Includes a press release in Spanish
      - AIDS Healthcare Workers, c. 1988, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 21)
        Includes Congress documents.
      - AIDS and Heterosexuals, 1987-1988 (Box 14, Folder 22)
      - AIDS and the Homeless, 1990, 1999-2000 (Box 14, Folder 23)
        Highlights of the National Survey of Homeless Assistance Providers and Clients
      - AIDS - Housing, 1994-2001 (Box 14, Folder 24)
        Includes Budget Summaries
      - AIDS - Institute of Human Virology, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 25)
      - AIDS - Insurance, 1988-1996 (Box 14, Folder 26)
      - AIDS - International, 1994-2001 (Box 14, Folder 27)
        Includes Report on the Presidential Mission on children Orphaned by AIDS in Sub-Saharan Africa
      - AIDS - IV Drugs, 1988-1995, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 28)
      - AIDS - Legal Rights, c. 1987-1993 (Box 14, Folder 29)
      - AIDS - Legislation, national, c. 1988, 1991, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 30)
      - AIDS - Legislation, New York State, 1989-1992 (Box 14, Folder 31)
        Notes, Assembly Regular Sessions, Releases from the executive chamber of former Gov. Mario M. Cuomo
      - AIDS and Lipodystrophy, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 32)
      - AIDS - Lobbying, 1987, 1992-1993, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 33)
      - AIDS - Mastery, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 34)
        Workshop Pamphlets and information
      - AIDS - Media, c. 1987-1996 (Box 14, Folder 35)
        Pamphlets, photos.
      - AIDS - Memorials, c. 1992-1996, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 36)
        Photo, email.
      - AIDS - Medical Waste, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 37)
      - AIDS - Medicine and Miracles - newsletter, 1993-1996, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 38)
      - AIDS and the Military, c. 1996 (Box 14, Folder 39)
        Memorandums.
      - AIDS - A new Norvir, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 40)
      - AIDS - MCC AIDS Resource Library, c. 1996-1997 (Box 14, Folder 41)
      - AIDS - Names Project, 1988-1996 (Box 15, Folder 1)
        Newspaper articles, newsletters, press releases, instructions, media kit, letters, photos
      - AIDS - Names Quilt Rochester, Undated (Box 15, Folder 2)
        Newspaper articles, brochures.
      - AIDS - Needle Exchange, c. 1997-2001 (Box 15, Folder 3)
        Newspaper articles, press releases, email.
      - AIDS - Network, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 4)
      - AIDS and Nutrition, c. 1994-1996 (Box 15, Folder 5)
        Press releases, booklets.
      - AIDS - NYC AIDS Commission, Undated (Box 15, Folder 6)
        Newspaper article.
      - AIDS - Office of National AIDS Policy, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 7)
      - AIDS - Origin Theories, c. 1987-1992, 1999-2000 (Box 15, Folder 8)
        Poster, articles, brochures and essays/excerpts.
      - AIDS - Pain Management, 1993-1995 (Box 15, Folder 9)
        Essays.
      - AIDS - Partner Notification and Names Reporting, c. 1997-1998 (Box 15, Folder 10)
        Copy of the partner notification bill.
      - AIDS and People of Color, c. 1989-2004 (Box 15, Folder 11)
        Brochures, pamphlets, photo, articles.
      - AIDS - Policies (federal), c. 1993-1995 (Box 15, Folder 12)
        Memorandum, pamphlet.
      - AIDS - Presidential Commission, 1987-1992 (Box 15, Folder 13)
      - AIDS - Prevention, c. 1992-1993, 1997-2002 (Box 15, Folder 14)
        Some documents in Spanish.
      - AIDS - Prisons, c. 1988, 1993, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 15)
        Issues of Justicia.
      - AIDS - Project Inform (1), 1997 (Box 15, Folder 16)
        Newsletters, press releases, letters addressed to Susan Jordan
      - AIDS - Project Inform (2), 1997-1999 (Box 15, Folder 17)
        Information packet, newsletters, press releases, letters addressed to Susan Jordan
      - AIDS - Project Inform (3), 1999-2003 (Box 15, Folder 18)
        Magnus newsletters, newsletters, letters addressed to Susan Jordan, media kit
      - AIDS Project Los Angeles, 1987-1988, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 19)
        Media Reports, newsletters
      - AIDS - RAFTA, c. 2000-2002 (Box 15, Folder 20)
        Pamphlet, Monthly Bulletin.
      - AIDS and Religion, Local, c. 1987-1992 (Box 15, Folder 21)
        Handwritten note, A Pastoral Instruction on the AIDS Crisis.
      - AIDS and Religion, 1987-1988, 1992-1994 (Box 15, Folder 22)
      - AIDS Remembrance Park (Rochester), c. 1995 (Box 15, Folder 23)
      - AIDS Research, c. 1987-2000 (Box 15, Folder 24)
      - AIDS - Vaccine Research, c. 1987-1999 (Box 15, Folder 25)
      - AIDS - Resource Center, c. 1995 (Box 15, Folder 26)
      - AIDS Rochester, Inc. (1), 1986-1995 (Box 15, Folder 27)
      - AIDS Rochester, Inc. (2), c. 1996-2003 (Box 15, Folder 28)
      - AIDS - Rural (see conferences), 1995-1996 (Box 15, Folder 29)
      - AIDS and Suicide, Undated (Box 15, Folder 30)
      - AIDS and HIV Service Agencies, c. 1997 (Box 15, Folder 31)
      - AIDS - Sexuality, 1997-1998 (Box 15, Folder 32)
      - AIDS - Sports, Undated (Box 15, Folder 33)
      - AIDS - Statistics, 1992,1997-1998 (Box 15, Folder 34)
      - AIDS - Support Groups, Undated (Box 15, Folder 35)
      - AIDS and Syphilis, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 36)
      - AIDS - TAG, 1995-1998 (Box 15, Folder 37)
      - AIDS Testing, c. 1987-1991, 1998-2000 (Box 15, Folder 38)
      - AIDS Testing - Local, c. 1988 - 1996 (Box 15, Folder 39)
      - AIDS Theories, c. 1987 (Box 15, Folder 40)
      - AIDS Therapies (aside from AZT), c. 1992-1998 (Box 15, Folder 41)
        Photograph.
      - AIDS Treatment News, 1995-1996 (Box 15, Folder 42)
      - AIDS Weeks - Oct. 1996 (D.C), 1996 (Box 15, Folder 43)
      - AIDS - Washburn, John, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 44)
      - AIDS - Women, c. 1987-1996 (Box 15, Folder 45)
        Some materials in French.
      - AIDS - World AIDS Day, c. 1988-1999 (Box 15, Folder 46)
        Poster.
      - AIDS and Youth, 1995-1996 (Box 15, Folder 47)
      - Airlines, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 48)
      - Alabama, 1997, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 49)
      - Alaska, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 50)
      - Albany, 1988, 1994, 1999-2000 (Box 16, Folder 1)
      - Alcoholism and Chemical Dependency, c. 1990-2001 (Box 16, Folder 2)
      - Allen, Kathleen, c. 1995 (Box 16, Folder 3)
      - Alternatives for Battered Women (ABW), 1987-2002 (Box 16, Folder 4)
      - Alumni, 1988-1995 (Box 16, Folder 5)